You guys quickly change to taking pictures.
My character is as pure as a flower.  I will
give money to those who wash their hands of me.
Do you understand this wedding food?  Today is my wedding.
Your son is looking for his daughter.  Look at Joy's
wife.
Happy anniversary.   Thank you.
We have found many gems here.
I wo
n't wear it today.
Hey Guy, Assalamu Alaikum.
And welcome to my blog.  Guys,
today's blog is very, very special.
Because this is our fourth year wedding
anniversary blog.  It seems like
we've been married for four years, guys.
Thank God.  It seems like Guy got
married that very day.  And four years
passed in between.  That means 1460 days.  Thank God.
Thank God.  Thank God.  We are
both very, very happy guys.  So guys,
we're going to celebrate our fourth anniversary in a big way.   I will
celebrate at night with Rakib Hossain from the Fast Guys team.  And tomorrow
we will celebrate together with the whole family.
So let's start our fourth
year wedding anniversary blog.
How are you feeling?  It's been
four years since we were married.
I can't believe it, guys.  I am married.  It's been
four years.  Oh my God.
I was single a few days ago, man.  I
still can't believe that
we've spent so many days together since our wedding.
Alhamdulillah, it's been
four years since we last saw each other.
We have to spend our whole lives together.  And
I'm even more excited now because soon
we'll be celebrating our anniversary in a big way.
I'm really excited for tomorrow, guys.
How do you like the song?  It's been
four years since we were married.   It
feels very good.  I could
n't believe how four years had passed.  And this
is for you.
Thank you Ritu Joy.  Tell me how you feel.
How else will I feel?  You are
celebrating your four-year anniversary after getting married.
Will you marry me?
You look so bad, you're not even a little happy.   He has a
little problem with his head.
Tell me, how do you feel about this life?   It's been
four years since I married you.
But why hasn't a guest come to the house yet
?
Guest.  What kind of guest is a guest again?   I do
n't understand why you say,
listen to me, if you had married me at the right time, I would have a
child as big as you now. Do you
know
what you are saying? They didn't get me married, this is a
slap, Marmu, I will get you
married. Don't tell me that, you wo
n't get married, your marriage will be canceled, that's why you have a
child as big as her.
I don't understand what's wrong with you. You've gone
crazy for marriage.
Here, I'm bringing flowers for you.
Happy fourth year anniversary.
This is what we're bringing. Do
I see it or are you lying?
Why did she give it to me? I gave it to you.
Okay, wait, you really did
n't bring me a flower.   I'm bringing this.   I
mean, I don't understand how changeable people are,
looking at you.
I made a mistake giving you the flower.  Let it
stay with me.  You don't deserve this.   It's
only been four [loud laughter] years and now they've
stopped bringing me flowers.   If I
give you so many billions of flowers, you won't say anything.
Go get the flowers now.
Where do you look for flowers at night?  Guys, on
the occasion of our fourth year anniversary, look at
how much Joy Jeevan Neetu is bringing.  Today,
we will create an anniversary stage with these.
Look how good they are.
How much for us?
Yes, actually.
How lucky are we, aren't we?
Very lucky.
Thank you so much guys.  I'm completely surprised that you brought so much for us.
I am very lucky.  I
've found such a great team member like you.  Now tell me,
whose plan is this?
I don't know anything, brother. I wasn't even here.
You mean you didn't have any plans?
I will make someone's plan.  You know, I ca
n't do anything for you, girl.
How bad is it?  You won't get married for the rest of your life.
You will be single all your life.  Surely the
season is coming.
No, brother, I can't endure this pain.
I did
n't bring you either?
No no no
so who is bringing it?
I don't want to bring any of them, uncle.  I am bringing the last month.   Did
you really bring it?
Yes.
Allah.  You have a very good life.
I'll feed you all the meat you need tomorrow, even if it's too much.
Eat until you are full.  We won't come
tomorrow then.  Okay.   Why not
?  Everyone should be there.  Why didn't you tell us
?
Yes, I will eat, I will eat you too.
We are no good if we don't work, and we are
better off if we work.
No, no, you are always good.
Yes.  So since he's bringing all that
money today,
This season, please do it with Joy.
I can't do anything for you without Joy.
I don't know, you can give it to whoever you want.
I won't.
Listen, you guys will do it on my anniversary.
I will do the same when your anniversary comes.
You won't marry me.  What
anniversary should I celebrate?  When they get married, they will
say, "Look, our kids are getting older. We have to
give
them time. You guys, do your thing.
This won't happen. This won't happen. We'll
work together.
You'll forget him later. Dad, I wo
n't forget.
What will happen to him?
You'll get old from my marriage. I'll get old from
your marriage. Am I that old? Am I
one year older than you? Am I
20 years older than you?
Brother, how old is he?
Five years old.
You're five. Then I have six guys. Let's
see what your team, Rakib Hossain, is
bringing for us.
Rakib Hossain, bring life.
When did you bring it?
I'm just bringing it.  It's not just me, it's all
three of them, the guys, who are blaming me.
Wow, the stage is so
beautiful.  But why is Happy Birthday written on the stage
?
He is bringing it.   That's why
God is
saying this and bringing it.  Would we have done
this if we had brought them here?
Why don't you write "Anniversary" or "Happy Birthday"?
I don't know, Dad, I don't know.
Okay, wait, wait.
Our wedding anniversary is our anniversary.   Okay guys, there are
a lot of balloons here.  Now
we will kill them all.  Okay.
Why?  We all have an anniversary, no, no,
listen, you should surprise me, you
understand, you're a fool, you just show me,
close your eyes, nothing,
I say, listen, you're afraid, get married, I'm a
girl,
I'll design with that girl, what's this
song?
I'm thinking, do
n't go, you're afraid, if you go, you'll never get married, what
kind of thing is this, your wife won't know, there won't be a wedding, you celebrate
my anniversary today, I'll bring
your wife by tomorrow, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, I'll have a lot of
beautiful girls come to my anniversary, I'll
make an arrangement from there, wait, wait, let's go
Balloons are inflated
Thank you so much Joy
Deal But don't be mistaken No
Deal I won't forget Inshallah You will get married soon You do
n't understand Are you
talking about tomorrow Inshallah And here guys Life is
inflating Cute One Life is inflating And all the
balloons here I will
inflate So less talk Now let's get to work quickly
[Music]
Finally Guys Alhamdulillah All the balloons are
inflated Complete Guys Inflating the balloons
All the oxygen in my head is gone Now
my head is spinning But I feel happy Finally All the
balloons are inflated Complete Guys
Today's life is also a lot of work Look at
how many balloons are already inflating
Thank you so much Life
Welcome And tomorrow But I can
eat a lot of food Polao Beef roast
Everything I will
feed everything There will be nothing left
Tomorrow there will be nothing left
Joy Thank you too You are working hard You are
not going to thank me today So father
then  What should I give, father?
You promised me that you would marry me tomorrow.
Please tell me something other than marriage.
You said that you will have many marriages here and
you will give me one from there.
Okay, I'll marry you tomorrow on my anniversary.   Sure, sure, okay guys,
we boys teams have everything ready.
Now I'll make a beautiful
anniversary stage with these.  So let's
start building the stage quickly without delay.
Guys, we, the boys team, are working so hard here,
and here you see them sitting and applying henna.
You sit there and look at the henna,
can you live like this?
I can give you better henna than this one.
We know that you give good henna.   It
really shows on Eid day.
Okay, we've talked about giving a patti patti. Are you feeling married or not?
Why are you applying henna like this?   So, it seems like there's a wedding
every year.
Anniversary means marriage.  Don't you know?
Brother, brother, what a drama.  Okay, I understand that
Antara is applying henna here.  And Asha is giving him henna.
But sister, what is your role
here?
So it's helping me a lot.   He is trying
to help in some way.
What are you just seeing?  In what way am I helping?   Will
you help me with my work?
I am needed here.
Look at the way these girls do things.
Inflating these balloons is the boys' job.   I do
n't understand why you have to give a surprise.
And the father and the girls will just get a surprise.   You
never give surprises, right?
No.
Girls are given jobs by girls.
You guys stay here.  Guys, today we will be setting up
our anniversary stage in this
corner.  So guys, we're going to
put two bolts on this wall.  I'm bringing two bracelets.
The guys have already taken off their gloves.
Because Joy is very
excited today.  I am very excited for tomorrow.   Do
n't say you're excited for today.   I will
marry you then.
You're getting married.
Yes, I'm very excited about today.
So guys, now we're going to put this in this corner nicely.
Guys, I'll give this king's crown to the top one time.
Now the two brothers will plant love in two corners.
Guys, we've been married for four years.
So these four will be between two loves.
Guys, after putting so much effort into filling out the Happy Birthday
letter, I realized I didn't put the Happy Birthday
letter on it.  What is this problem?
Hey, if you put Happy Birthday here, it will hurt.  I wo
n't wear it.  Go away.
What?
I've been blowing my nose for an hour now,
this is the result.
Your nose is running, your head is sweating, your feet are swollen.
Anyway, I'm shedding it.
No, no, guys.  This will look very bad if you wear it.
So I cancel it.   They are
swollen.  I like that.
No, I used to put happy birthday on my anniversary day
or you go.
So now I and Joy are
decorating this place with balloons. It's not getting any better. Guys, look at
this. The girls are not getting any more henna.
Brother, you are giving mehendi. You are getting some more henna.
Look at this. Guys, the
season is not over.
Why are you
sleeping? Where are you sleeping? I have closed my eyes. You don't understand. Are
you sleeping? Are you giving me rest?
Yes, I have been looking at you for a long time. He
has given mehendi on both hands.
Brother, hurry up. Hurry up. The day is
passing by.
Almost by the way. Guys, look at
Asara's
talent and how beautifully he has given mehendi.
Hope, tell me who taught you henna.
Uncle,
this is the truth. Thank you.
I want to tell you something. Just like
uncle, there is no such thing as a brother.
My nephew will be like me.
Uncle lies and nieces lie too.
[Voice]  [Laughs]
We lie and say, "Something happened, what happened to me? Leave me alone, do
n't listen to them. You understand, guys,
our anniversary cake is coming. Let's
unpack our anniversary cake and show it to you. We bought Guy Red this time.
Since Guy Red is my favorite
color, I bought a cake in a completely unique style. By
God, I put it here as soon as I unpacked it.
No problem, Guy. I'm fixing it now. It's
fixed. Guys, I personally like the cake
a lot. There's
a candle on top of it. Now we'll fit it in.
Just look how
much nicer it looks after applying it.  Guys, look at the candle
holder on the right.  Look
how much nicer it looks after applying it.  A completely royal
vice is coming.  Wow,
I'll put the candles in the cake nicely now.
[Music]
Complete Guy.  Look how much more beautiful it
looks now.  Wow.
[Music]
Finally guys our fourth year wedding
anniversary stage is ready
guys look how beautiful the stage has become I did
n't expect it to be so beautiful
Joy helped me a lot
thank you so much Joy
our deal but there is dad
dad please do
n't stop thank you life too
I won't take it thanks you are telling Joy well
you are young so
I am helping more pulao roast meat I will
eat everything tomorrow to my stomach thank you thank you thank you so much
welcome guys it's my anniversary
boys you have to take a little party look right
boys you can do everything
how do you feel
today is your birthday birthday and
anniversary same thing be it my birthday and
my wedding birthday all ghee right come on guys
now let's bring Antara today guys who will make Antara
cry with happiness when she sees the stage guys
her son in law is working so hard  The stage has been
set up, so don't delay, let's
hurry up and bring Antra.
What
stage are you setting up? You're setting up
alone. You do
n't need to tell her in front of her. Everyone says I'm setting up alone. She was
sitting there. I'm
doing everything alone. Guys, now I'll go and bring Antra. What kind of surprise is
this? Hey, anniversary, surprise, guys.
I don't understand, is it an anniversary
or a birthday party?
Why don't you like it?
Happy birthday is being celebrated here.
Anniversary is being celebrated. Nothing is being celebrated in Bangladesh. That's
why Happy Birthday. Hey,
I say, one is the birthday of one person.
Today is the birthday of both. So, yes,
today is my and Antara's wedding birthday. This is our first
wedding birthday.
I haven't seen it before.
And that's why I'm setting up a very beautiful stage for you. You know, if
you see it, you'll cry with happiness.
Come on, guys.
Now hurry up and surprise Antara.
Today is my wedding, give me a broken doll. Today is my
wedding, give me a good doll. Give me a good doll.
Guys.  I'm coming now, I'll
surprise Antara. Guys, are you ready for one?
[Screaming]
When did you decorate these? You know, you
decorated them all with great difficulty alone. Oh my God, the
sweat on my forehead has gone down to my feet.
You really decorated them all alone.
Yes, I decorated them with great difficulty. You know, long
live Jeevan. They didn't help me even a little bit.
They were so bad.
Dad was suffering a lot. You
should have helped me.
Sorry, Mama. My eyes hurt.
I knew you would do it. You're
suffering a lot. Thank you. Don't
cry. [Loud laughter] [Crying] Keep going.
[Loud laughter]
Guys, now we're lighting our candles.
I'm so excited to celebrate my
wedding anniversary.
Wedding anniversary.
Wow guys, look how much prettier the cake
looks now, doesn't it?
Come on, come on, let's cut it.
Happy birthday to my marriage.  Anniversary
[loud laughter]
Wedding.
Happy birthday to my marriage.   It's been
four months already.
Happy birthday to my marriage.  Happy birthday,
wedding, happy anniversary,
anniversary,
happy anniversary,
look, man, it's tasty, eat now, get
married, don't eat, get married, good morning, Aviwan,
man, today is our main wedding
anniversary celebration with the family,
but unfortunately, man, I have
n't been able to buy a dress yet.  So now I'll go
buy a dress and Antara will go to
the parlor to get dressed.
Yes, I don't have to get ready nicely, it's
our anniversary today.
You could dress up at home.  Do
you need to go to the parlor?
Yes, you need to style your hair nicely.   It's acting like
Antara is
really getting married today.   Hey, I'm getting
married.  This is a very nice
get-together family program.
Oh guys, we won't be late again.  I'll go
buy a dress soon.  And Antara will
come dressed quickly.  Okay.   Come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.  Guys, we are coming. Today we came to the
run. Guys, we have chosen our dress.
Our anniversary
theme this year is Guys Off White.
This one was the most beautiful of all the off white ones. So, I have chosen it.
How do you like it?
I like it very much.
It will go perfectly with my outfit.
Guys, I like it a lot. Let me
try it on a little or I will read it at home. If
you want, I tried on the
dress a little. I
like it a lot. You see, it
looks much more beautiful after reading it. Now, I have
not read the half-plaid pants.
I will wear the pants during the ceremony.  How
does the ball feel now?
It looks very beautiful.  I always
like Azran's outfits.
I like guys a lot more.  I'm
not always one of those guys.  So this is what
we are reading on our anniversary.  Guys, I'm
buying my anniversary outfit confirmation in just two minutes.  Because
I'm dizzy looking at all the beautiful collections they have here
?
This is very beautiful.  I personally
feel much better.
Guy is now going to the parlor.   Come
quickly from the parlor and get dressed.  Okay.
You don't say anything, guys, I'm two
hours late.
Hurry up, hurry up.  Bye
bye.
Tata.
Guys, I'm back home.
Guys, I'm bringing an anniversary gift for Antara when I get home.
Guys, this time I'm gifting him a
camera.  This is basically
Guy Antara's favorite camera.
Guys, this camera is not available anywhere.
We are looking for a lot in Thailand.   I did
n't find it in Thailand, I did
n't find it in Canada either.  So finally, guys, I found a shop in Bangladesh
where they pre-ordered and brought it to
me.  So I
ordered this while I was in Canada and
finally I received it today.  So
I'll quickly rap this now and I hope the
guys will be very happy if they get it today.
So now
I'll quickly wrap the gift.
Finally, guys, our gift wrapping is
complete.  Look, guys, how beautifully I'm
rapping.  Hey guys, it's
5:30 in the afternoon now.  All the guests will
arrive at the venue by seven in the evening.  So now I'll hurry up and take a
shower and get ready.
Shower complete guys, now I'll
set my hair.
Guys, today I will make Get
Ready with Me with you.  So I'm coming with my sherwani.
Now I will read the poem.
Guys, let me know how you like the sherbet.
I personally
like this a lot, guys.  Guys, I'll
read the crores so fast.
[Music] Guy, now I'll read the top part of this.
Wow guys.  Look how beautiful I
look.  Guys, today I'm
reading by matching my outfit.  Look at these shoes, they
match my entire dress.
Mashallah, Mashallah, Mashallah.
Look how much better your favorite YouTuber
looks today.  Number one look on YouTube,
number one, Alhamdulillah.
Thank God.  Alhamdulillah guys.  I did
n't expect it myself.  I
feel so beautiful today.  Just look at
how beautiful I
look on my anniversary.  And how much
more beautiful will it look on the day I dress up as a son-in-law?  I'm very
excited, guys.
Guys, my boys' team is already coming to see me as a son-in-law. So
let's go to the boys' team now. Hello boys,
hello.
How do I feel? I don't feel like a son-in-law.
Dad, look, nod your head. I don't feel like a son-in-law.
Yes, I do.
And are you reading this? Your
blazer is much bigger than yours. Do
you understand this? This is the style of 2030. The
style of 2030. How many years are there now?
I upgraded four years in 2026. I do
n't understand these. These are studies, studies,
and my God. Bye. Why are you reading so gorgeous today? Hey, don't you have to see a
girl there? I do
n't understand this. Brother, it's my anniversary. I
think she's more gorgeous than me.
You said you'll see a girl for me there.
All the girls there are too. Sorry. I'm married.
You want my girl, why not? I do
n't want your girl.
I'll find a girl for you. Look in your
mind.
Promise, promise, promise. Guys,
this is the season.  Looking at the upcoming season, I
feel like an Arabian girl today. I am
wearing an Arabian look today.
Ritu looks much more beautiful today, guys.
I made a caftan today.   It's
great that you like it so much.
Guys, mom is getting ready and
coming.  Mom looks much more
beautiful today.  How do you like me, Mom
?   I
like it.
So tell me, how are you feeling?  It's been
four years since your son got married.  And in
a few days, we'll have our wedding ceremony.
But guys, we'll have a lot more
fun at the wedding.  Isn't that right, Mom?   It'll
be a lot of fun, guys.  And for the first time
today mom got ready so quickly thank
you so much mom guys we are all ready
and look Antar is still sitting in the parlor
how much more time will it take you
I will need another five hours
five hours then you don't need to come
you stay here ok bye let's
see how your makeup is apart from the mobile
why don't you show me now I will show you the finale absolutely what happened ok
come quickly finally
guy
ready guy now we will quickly go to the venue
all our guests are coming
waiting for us.  So let's not be late, guys.   Let's
go.
Guys, I feel like I'm being tickled too much.
Why tickle?   Hey, don't
you understand that if you go here, you'll get something.
What will I get?
Hey, my wife.  [ __ ], [ __ ],
how do people get a wife before marriage?
You promised me you would bring me a wife
tomorrow.
How can your wife not give you a mirror?  If you get married, you will
get a wife.
You said you'd take a look at my wife from here.   I
mean, I'll find a girl.
Yes, you said yesterday.
Yes, that's what you're saying, being so mischievous.  No no
[Loud laughter] No I don't understand mischief I have to
find it
Okay I'll try and see if I can
find someone like you So say
yes Promise
Okay Promise I do
n't need any more touching
Okay Promise
Promise
Mother Joy who keeps getting married and getting married used to
say when will she get married
After five more years Five more
years You heard that you will get married After five more years
Nanu's daughter You don't have to look for Rana's daughter You already know that
you are looking for Nana Nana wo
n't look for Apu Joy
When will she get married
After five years
Baapre Ritu What do you want When will her marriage be
When Allah writes marriage on her forehead Then
marriage will automatically happen.
Look, the drama is going to his book fight.
Mom says five years, Dad says five years.   In
total, she will get married after 10 years.
Which you will get married in 10 years.  You are single.
You die.
Those who get married too many times never get
married.  Don't you know?
No, I don't know that.  You know this on condition that
you find my daughter.  You think about it.
You won't get married.
[Music]
Guys, I'm coming to the venue. I've
found guys. Antara
doesn't show her face. Her face is hidden. Now turn around and
see.
Your look has become much more beautiful. You look
beautiful to me. You look beautiful. You look beautiful.
So beautiful. Tell me how you look.
You look beautiful too. You look very beautiful. Perfectly
matching. Matching.
Matching. Guys. Antara is getting dressed
in the parlor and I am getting dressed at home. Who
looks more beautiful? Everyone will comment and tell me.
Your sons, if they want, can we get dressed in the parlor
or we do
n't need to dress up in our parlor.
We are just like that. Natural
beauty guys. Will my father find a wife for me? He is
busy with his own wife. If I don't want to be
busy with my wife, then what should I be busy with? I wo
n't be busy with my wife. Why should I be busy with your wife? What do you say to
him? But I will really give you my heart today.
My wife, do
n't ruin my special day,
we'll take pictures.   Do
n't make this my special day.
Guys, okay, but I'll give you my opinion.
I will stay, but I will go.  Go ahead, go ahead.
Okay, listen, listen, let's borrow the flower,
see if you can do it now.
Hold the flower in your hand and see if anyone notices.
I gifted Antar a flower on the occasion of the guy's anniversary.  Here you go.
A blanket with him.  Look at how beautiful a shawl I
brought for you.
Yes, the guys are bringing me so many things.
Look.
Now, guys, I'll teach Antara this.  Here,
wife, I put a veil on you.
You are covering my makeup. This
veil is too big. What should I do?
Yes, I have to set it. Now, set it quickly.
Guys, look how beautifully I have put
a tail on Antara. Now Antara is looking like a
prince.
Sorry Antara, now princess. Let's
take a picture. Come on. Guys, there are
many mosquitoes here. That's why Antara is
taking pictures so that mosquitoes
cannot disturb Antara.
You don't understand anything. You will really remain famous for the
rest of your life.
So what are you doing with the net?
How do you do this? You don't know. I have never seen wives
take pictures like this.
How can I see if I am getting married first?
Then watch it now. I have to
take it in the program in front of me. Okay, okay, guys.
This is basically
not for mosquitoes. Sleep.
Yes,
I misunderstood. Sorry, guys. Antara was
alone inside the mosquito net for so long. Now it has taken me too. Yes,
come on. There are many mosquitoes. If mosquitoes
give you clothes, that's why I am putting them in at once.
Yes, there are two of us now.  I'm going to go inside the mosquito net and take pictures, right? Guys,
what day has come after my wedding that I have to go
inside the mosquito net and take pictures now? That's why
I'm asking you to stay on the signal until you get married,
right?
Joy is really going to get married again, do
n't you understand?
Harm, harm, wherever it comes from, go ahead and
disturb it.   I
understand, father, go away, you spoiled boy. I don't
understand why you only
want to get married with clothes. Do you know how much money and trouble it takes to get married
?   You're talking about
money problems, you're thinking about your uncle here.
How am I feeling?
Whatever it may seem, I say don't get married.   Get
these demons out of your head.  Because getting
married is the biggest mistake in the world.   I feel
a little ashamed.  You
can date any girl you want now,
then you can go out and travel, you
can get married,
but once you tell me the truth, if you get married, you will have to live with
someone like me, her
character is not good, you can't live with someone,
my character is as pure as a flower,
since your character is not good, why will you get married?
You will fall in love,
and Guy Babu is coming, come, Guy,
look at my call, Izan Babu,
Babu, say hi to everyone, hello everyone,
Izan Babu is coming, Izan Babu is
looking very beautiful today, Mashallah, and in a few days
we will have a baby like this, right?
Inshallah, Allah willing, it will definitely happen, why
not?
Look how cute she looks, baby, baby, guys, I like her a lot, my
heart wants me to take her, she will
cry, it wo
n't be right to be late, come quickly,
Inshallah, guys, we
were waiting for our program, when the program is done,
Inshallah, guys, your waiting will be over,
next year, Inshallah, Junior
Rakib will come, right?
Yes, Junior  Rakib and Junior can come in the background,
whatever Allah gives,
Inshallah, whatever we give, we will be happy with that.
Guys, when will we come? It will be almost an hour
plus now, many people are taking pictures. They have
n't eaten since morning. They woke up and are
ready to come here. And they are not finished taking pictures.
I am very hungry. Please don't tell me quickly. I am also very hungry. Please, brother, finish taking pictures.
We will eat.
I am very hungry. So I don't need to take any more pictures.
Hey, sister, tell me what to do. At our real wedding,
we will take pictures.
Okay, after eating, we will take them again.
Okay, let's take a few more. I
think you have taken 1000 pictures. I will
take one or two. It's not too much. I
will post them at 10 or 12. What are you going to do with all of them? Hey, we have to
find a good one among all of them.
We all eat them up.
No, no, please, go ahead. We have to
take pictures with you. Wait, hurry up. Guys, I am tired of
taking pictures. That's why I am coming to
eat.  After eating, I will get
energy and then take pictures again. You can see
here, Ratu ma'am, I took it with me.
Ma'am, you know how the wedding
food looks. Today is my wedding. Finally,
my ladies team's
right to take food. Now, they are serving food here.
Guys, now we will eat the wedding food. The
wedding food is so much fun. The
food is getting
restless. Look, guys, you are seeing how
bad it is. Meanwhile, I can't eat. Look
at me. Don't even look at how my wife will
eat. Let me make some arrangements.
Why don't you eat with your hands?
Look at the condition of my hands. It doesn't matter.
Today is a special day.
Okay, I will feed you. Give it to me. The
wedding food is a lot of fun.
Guys, I got into trouble when I came to eat. Now, look at
how many parties are coming. They all
wash our hands. I didn't get a
chance to wash my hands during the wedding.
Today, but somehow, I will miss the chance. Now, if I wash it, it will be
during the wedding program. But I wo
n't get the money for washing it.   You
have to pay double.
No, no, no, no, no.
Since the guys are coming to wash.   I wo
n't say anything today.
I'm stealing a flower specially for my brother-in-law.
[ __ ], even if you bring a flower, it will still be stolen.
What should I do?  [Music]
No, no, clean it.  You won't get the money.  You will get burned.
My wife has come with me.  Now the
elder sister will wash the wife's hands.  Guys, the
plates are being prepared for the books here, what's up,
brother, wash your clean hands again
[Music]
Now I'll
give money to those who are washing my hands [Loud laughter] Hey, those
who are washing me,
I only have dollars, okay, two
sisters come, two dollars to two sisters, one for
you and one for you,
this is the season
[Cheers]
[Screaming]
My head is spinning when I try to take pictures, but no
one is taking pictures, please
finish taking pictures quickly
[Screaming]
You are the ones taking pictures, we
can barely do it, quickly take pictures,
what happened, Joy, why are you upset?
The event is ending, you started it,
Mama, hey,
I can see the girl, I was very busy,
let's see now,
you won't talk, let's see,
everyone is gone, let's go,
everyone seems to be gone, is there
anyone here for Joy, listen to me,
this is Asma Apu, is there anyone here for Joy,
your son is looking for a girl, is there any girl here for your son, I do
n't think so  No, not here.
Actually, I don't think so either. Don't get upset. I
know where you are. Then they are talking to you
and asking you to look for her. Listen to me.
I am thinking that you should not give a tour to the country where you are. In every country,
you are a bad woman like your son. What am I
saying? I will get married in every country. Why are
you sitting here? Joy, why are you
looking for someone? We are your aunt,
you are her sister. That's why we won't look for her.
Dad, everyone here is selfish. You are selfish.
We don't know. We will only hurt her. There are no
girls here. She does
n't even believe in her.
Here, we are all relatives. Where can we find a girl?
We mix with someone outside. Guys,
after a lot of trouble, we found a wife.
Look, Joy's wife,
bring Joy. Guys, now
I will bring Joy.  Joy will go
crazy with happiness when she sees her wife.
Yes, go ahead.
I'm bringing him back soon.
Joy, I found your wife.
Really?
Really, come on.   Aren't you
kidding?   Come here, come  Are
you ready?
Yes.  Your wife is pulling three to one.   I
brought your wife.
This is a sleepover.   Wake up.
New wife.
[Screaming]
Joy's wife.
This is Nanu.
Who is Nanu?  Your wife.
This is the girl we got.   Did
you like your husband?
Yes, I liked it.
This is what the wife liked.
Well, no problem, the rest is outside the country.
Bangladesh, who are
you going to marry after marrying my mother
?
How dare you?
You will be happy with someone.  Okay?   From
today on, when you talk about Joy and his wife,
everyone will put up a picture of Ammu.  Your wife.
His marriage is final.  Finally guys,
our anniversary cake is coming.  And
look, guys, how beautiful our cake has
become.  How do you like the cake, Ritu?   It
feels much better.  Very beautiful cake.
Guys, look at this guy putting my name on the cake.  It's already
installed here.
Guys, look how beautiful our cake has
become.  And do you know who made this cake?  I did
n't make this, you made it.  Brother, you have magic in your hands.
Look at how beautiful the cake you made is.  Please
teach me a little too.   Sure.   Sure.
Guys, I just gave you a picture.
You made it much more beautiful than the picture.
I never imagined it would be exactly like this.  It's
been very, very good.  Cake is not only beautiful to look at,
it's also a lot more fun to eat.  Because
every cake you make is so much more yummy.   At
our house.
When is the wedding?  You are also saying when is the wedding?
Everyone has one question: When is our wedding
program?
Inshallah, will our wedding cake be this
big?  Inshallah.  Inshallah.  Inshallah,
you will receive an invitation this year.  InshaAllah.
Inshallah.
Guys, finally, we will cut our fourth year
anniversary cake.  Sing it.  Come on.
Happy anniversary.
Happy anniversary.   Thank you.
[Screaming]
Guys are saying goodbye in their hearts, everyone is crying,
look.
You don't take my sister.
So you go with it.   Okay, come on.
Hey, don't cry.  I am close to my son-in-law
[crying][screaming] and
they are both good people.
Yes, yes, very good people.  You are
not well, don't pray to God, He
knows you can be well like this. Let me
tell you something. Guys, mom, I
cried at my wedding. I love you.
Mom, I have been crying for two or three months.
My daughter has been crying for two or three months.
Okay, guys, why should we cry? My
heart is very close to Rakib.
[Loud laughter] I will
pray more and more so that they can be better.
[Cheers][Screaming] I am coming
home. Look, guys,
how many gifts we have received on our anniversary.  Oh
my God!  Besides that, guys, look how much
money I got.  Guys, I'm going to travel abroad with this money.   Does
this mean you are going to travel abroad?   The
two of us will go together.
Yes, it's for both of us.
Hey, the two of us will go together.   Shall we
buy something together?  Yes.
Besides that, guys, we have
received many gifts here.  Now we will unbox two gifts.
Mithu Bhai gave this to me.
And he gave this.  I'm very excited to
see you.  What's inside it?  Let me open it before you, okay okay okay, oh my
God, so that this gift is
mine, Antara, so that it doesn't happen,
it will be
mine
[shouting] Guys, this is
Payal, this is Antara, you see,
I said, now let me see this, this will be
mine, look,
this will be Aunty, it seems to be mine,
yes, it can be mine, let me see,
ready, one, two and three,
this is also Antara's, guys, earrings,
guys, all the gifts are mine [shouting] Wow,
I like it a lot.  Let's do some more
unboxing.  Let's do more unboxing
next.   Okay guys,
now we'll do the next unboxing.
This is given by Shuvo brother, come on.
Let's see what Shuvo Bhai's gift is.
Wow,
this is a photo frame.
Wow.
This was given to us by our
roomie.  Yes.  I forgot what the job was.
Hey, open it.  Guys, we got
two candle holders here.  Which is a
work of the heart.  I don't like candles.
Again, this is my job.  It's two for two,
meaning it's for two people.
Well [loud laughter] Okay.
Guys, now we will open the gift from Banya Apu.
What could it be?
It seems like something family-related.
Family.
That's what I wanted.  That's what we
needed, guys.  I have pretty much everything at home.  But one thing
comes to my mind.   A
very good idea.
The color is very beautiful.  It feels great.
Thank you so much, sister.  Now we will unbox
Sumi Apu's gift.
Yes, my older sister gave me this gift. I'm
very excited.   There's
a Punjabi saree in this,
right?
Yes, yes, it could be. Let's see,
where is Punjabi?
Where is Punjabi?  Guys, this is
just Antara's saree.   Oh
my God, look how beautiful your saree is.
Today, everything is just obstacles.
Wow, what a beautiful saree.  Thank you, ma'am.
Such a beautiful saree.  You are happy.
No, I'm very happy.  I did
n't feel like buying it.  I can't find it.  Next, we will be unboxing
Robait Apu's gift.  You
gave two gifts to two very nice people.
Wow, Antara has so many bags.
Yours looks so beautiful.
Let's see, guys, what's mine?  Wow, the packaging is
so beautiful.  I really like the Wow Box.
Wow.
Golden colored watch.
Wow, it's so beautiful.
Look at how beautiful the watch is.  Thank
you so much, sister, for giving me such a beautiful watch.
Personally, I like this song very much.
Now we will be unboxing the
gift given by the TRH Shop member and Antara
will be unboxing the
gift given by the Sunflower Team member.
I'm so excited to see it.
Me too.
Wow, they gave me a very beautiful
Punjabi set.  Wow, I like this a lot.
Thank you so much.   Wait, let me
see what you gave me.   I
gave you a sari.
Wow guys, look
how similar our members are.  Punjabi gave me a saree first.
Guys, look how similar our shop members are.
They wisely gave me a saree and you a
Punjabi.
And look, there are two matching results here.
We will read together.
Thank you so much.
Thank you guys for giving such a beautiful gift.
Guys, there are a total of three gifts now.
Antara will give me these two gifts.  And
I'm bringing this gift for Antara.  I will
give this to Antara.
But I gave you another gift before.
Yes, and I also know what's inside these two.
Yes.  I'm buying it from Canada because of him.
Let's unbox now.  But you, I don't
want to see you first, I'll see
yours first, I'll share it with everyone, and guys,
look, Antar gifted me a
Dyson hair dryer,
right, guys, why would I have a Dyson alone?
My husband
needs a
Dyson. I'm showing you another one, I
know that too. Then I'll see you
because everything is Rakib's favorite. Guys, is this
a shoe? Look, the
shoe is very beautiful. Thank you, welcome. We're
buying it together from Canada, but
what am I bringing for Antara? Antara does
n't know. You know, it's
very
true.
Let's unbox
what are you bringing?
Whatever you bring, you'll like it. Guys, it looks
very good.
You guess what it could be. I'll
guess whether it's makeup or
not. You like makeup so much. That's why
I bought you makeup today too. Open it or
not.
Seriously,
yes, your favorite is
Markoth and my God!  When are you bringing this?
Thank you guys, there will be plenty of pictures from now on.
Aesthetic aesthetic picture.  Wow.
This is your camera, Antara's camera,
Antara will take aesthetic photos with it.  Hey
guys, the camera is on.  Now you just
open the flash like this and take a picture.
Wow.  Are the pictures coming out beautiful?
And happy.
Very happy.  Thank you so much.
Welcome.
We've come to the end of today's blog.
This was our fourth
year wedding anniversary blog, guys.  This is the
first time we guys have celebrated our anniversary.
How did you like it?
I feel much better.  First of all, it
was a family get-together.  And it
feels so good.  I really like our look
today, finally.
We enjoyed it a lot with the family.
Please let me
know in the comments how you all feel.  So we
end our blog today here.
See you on the next blog.  Until then,
everyone stay well, stay healthy,
and pray for us more.
Allah is the protector.